cgiguangzhou.gov.in 2016-12-21

# Consulate General Of India

  * #### Announcements

Odisha State is fast emerging as the manufacturing hub of the East in India through its industry friendly environment and policy framework. 

More News

  * #### Consulate News

More News

  * #### India News

The Ministry of Tourism has introduced a 24x7 Toll Free Multi-Lingual Tourist Help Line to facilitate visits of foreign tourist visiting India.

More News

  * #### Events organised by Consulate General of India, Guangzhou

The Consulate General of India in Guangzhou is organzing a painting exhibition of Modern India titled “Modern India: Color, Pattern and Life” from 21st to 26th November, 2016. 

More News

  * #### International Day of Yoga 

The 2nd International Day of India (IDY) in Southern China was celebrated in five cities jointly organized by the Consulate General of India, Guangzhou with the local Municipality governments and other Yoga Institutes. 

More News

Thank you for visiting the website of the Consulate General of India in Guangzhou and reviewing our privacy policy. We do not collect any personal information about you other than what you choose to provide us.

_**Internet Security Policy**_

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, this system employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this service are strictly prohibited. 

_**Information Collected and Stored Automatically**_

When you browse through the website, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit: 

\- The Internet domain and IP address from which you access our website; 

\- The type of browser and operating system you use; 

\- The date and time of your access; 

\- The pages you visit;

\- The external links you choose to visit.

\- We use this information to help us make our site user-friendly.

_**When you choose to send us personal information**_

If you choose to provide us with personal information by sending an e-mail, or by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it through our website, we use that information to respond to your message and to help us provide you with information that you request. We do not collect personal information for any other purposes. The information you provide will not be given to any private organizations or private persons. 

_**Links to Other Sites**_

Our website has links to the websites of many other Government of India agencies. In a few cases, we link to private organizations. All external links open in a new window. Once you link to another site, you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site. 

_**Disclaimer**_

Links to third party websites or contents should not be construed as endorsement of any sort.

In no event shall Consulate General of India, Guangzhou be liable for any special, indirect or consequential damages or any damages whatsoever resulting from loss of use, data or profits, arising out of or in connection with the use of information available from the services of this website.
